<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Arcata Food Not Bombs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Arcata Food Not Bombs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Food Not Bombs Food Not Bombs is an all-volunteer movement that recovers food that would otherwise be discarded, and shares free vegan and vegetarian meals with the hungry in over 1,000 cities in 65 countries in protest to war, poverty, and destruction of the environment.
We arrange the collection of produce, bread and other food that can&amp;rsquo;t be sold from grocery stores, bakeries, and produce markets. They put this food to the side and we pick it up at a scheduled time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can get in touch with any of our active memebers through the following methods:
Email: contact@arcatafoodnotbombs.org
Phone (text messages preferred): (707) 840 - 4610
Instagram: Message @foodnotbombsarcata</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/donate/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to help our cause but do not have the time or ability to get involved, please consider donating to the group:
Extra Produce? We are always happy to take any extra produce and use it to help feed more people. Reach out to us through the Contact Us page on this site and we will be happy to help arrange a pickup or drop off that works for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/events-announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events-announcements/</guid>
      <description>Announcements: We are once again cooking out of the Spoon house, which has proven to be an awesome space for Food Not Bombs. We would like to thank everyone there for sharing their kitchen with us as well as everyone who offered us kitchen space and brought locations to our attention while we were looking.
We now have a shared email and google voice number that people can use to contact the group, see the new Contact Us page on this site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>Food Not Bombs Arcata is looking for volunteers, advocates and allies. We glean produce from the Arcata Co-op and Murphy&amp;rsquo;s in order to cook and serve free vegan meals every Sunday on the Arcata Plaza at 4PM.
Anyone can stop by to help serve food with us and this is a great way to meet the group and start helping.
We are always looking for volunteers to join us for any role during our Sunday schedule:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
